// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the full form of “AI”",
    answer: "Artificial Intelligence",
    options: [
      "Artificially Intelligent",
      "Artificial Intelligence",
      "Artificially Intelligence",
      "Advanced Intelligence"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is Artificial Intelligence?",
    answer: "Artificial Intelligence is a field that aims to develop intelligent machines",
    options: [
      "Artificial Intelligence is a field that aims to make humans more intelligent",
      "Artificial Intelligence is a field that aims to improve the security",
      "Artificial Intelligence is a field that aims to develop intelligent machines",
      "Artificial Intelligence is a field that aims to mine the data"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is the inventor of Artificial Intelligence?",
    answer: "John McCarthy",
    options: [
      "Geoffrey Hinton",
      "Andrew Ng",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Jürgen Schmidhuber"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the branch of Artificial Intelligence?",
    answer: "Machine Learning",
    options: [
      "Machine Learning",
      "Cyber forensics",
      "Full-Stack Developer",
      "Network Design"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " What is the goal of Artificial Intelligence?",
    answer: "To explain various sorts of intelligence",
    options: [
      "To solve artificial problems",
      "To extract scientific causes",
      "To explain various sorts of intelligence",
      "To solve real-world problems"
    ]
  },


    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is an application of Artificial Intelligence?",
    answer: "Language understanding and problem-solving (Text analytics and NLP)",
    options: [
      "It helps to exploit vulnerabilities to secure the firm",
      "Easy to create a website",
      "Language understanding and problem-solving (Text analytics and NLP)",
      "It helps to deploy applications on the cloud"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In how many categories process of Artificial Intelligence is categorized?",
    answer: "categorized into 3 categories",
    options: [
      "categorized into 5 categories",
      "processes are categorized based on the input provided",
      "categorized into 3 categories",
      "process is not categorized"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Based on which of the following parameter Artificial Intelligence is categorized?",
    answer: "Based on capabilities and functionally",
    options: [
      "Based on functionally only",
      "Based on capabilities only",
      "Based on capabilities and functionally",
      "It is not categorized"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Which of the following is a component of Artificial Intelligence?",
    answer: "Learning",
    options: [
      "Learning",
      "Training",
      "Designing",
      "Puzzling"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the function of an Artificial Intelligence “Agent”?",
    answer: "Mapping of precept sequence to an action",
    options: [
      "Mapping of goal sequence to an action",
      "Work without the direct interference of the people",
      "Mapping of precept sequence to an action",
      "Mapping of environment sequence to an action"
    ]
  },
];